(Silence; Operating Room Area)
=Stand Up for Love=
=Episode 1=
(Zhang Haotian.)
(I've already altered
the donation agreement for you.)
(The psychiatric hospital is arranged.)
(You took Miss Jiang's kidney)
(and tricked the Lin family's
heiress into marrying you.)
(You promised you'd pay off
my gambling debts.)
(Jiang Lai, a dance prodigy betrayed
in love and robbed of her kidney)
(So when are you giving me the money?)
(If we don't get rid of her,)
(we're both going down with her.)
(Zhang Haotian, a heartless man who used
marriage to steal Jiang Lai's kidney)
(He's my fiance,)
(Zhang Haotian.)
(Jiang Lai, will you marry me?)
(I'll spend my whole life
protecting you.)
(On the eve of our wedding,)
(he was diagnosed with uremia.)
(I was a perfect match for him.)
(Party B's Thumbprint: Jiang Lai)
(I gave him one of my kidneys.)
(But he...)
(was a liar.)
(This man is his accomplice.)
(For their own selfish gain,)
(Chen Ping, the corrupt doctor
who removed Jiang Lai's kidney)
(they conspired against me.)
(They didn't just steal my kidney.)
(Organ Transport Container)
(They wanted me to go forever)
(and deliberately framed me
as mentally unstable.)
(Once she's locked away
in a psychiatric hospital,)
(she'll never get out.)
(Then the problem will take care
of itself.)
(Zhang Haotian.)
(You destroyed my life.)
(I'll send you straight to hell.)
(I have to survive.)
(I have to get revenge!)
(Has anyone ever experienced)
(falling from heaven straight
into hell?)
(I have.)
(Because right now, I'm in hell.)
(My name is Jiang Lai.)
(I was a gifted dancer who belonged
on center stage.)
(The person I loved most)
(destroyed my dreams
and buried my entire life)
(with his own hands.)
(Private Hospital; Outpatient Department)
Mai, when did you come back?
If I hadn't returned,
you'd have lost your life.
(Zhao Mai, Jiang Lai's best friend,
a wealthy returnee)
I know what happened.
What can I do to help?
I want revenge.
Shouldn't we call the police first?
No.
I want to send him to hell myself.
Then I'll help you make it happen.
I'll make everyone who hurt you
pay the price.
Right now,
he must be using my kidney
to climb into wealth and power.
I looked into it.
(Su Qinglan, Jingzhou's richest woman)
Su suffered kidney failure for 3 years.
(Lin Lulu's mother)
She just underwent a kidney transplant.
(Lin Lulu, a wealthy heiress)
And she's Lin Lulu's mother.
(I love you, Lin Lulu!)
Then there's no doubt.
Lin Lulu is Zhang Haotian's new target.
He's using my kidney as his ticket
into the Lin family
to steal their fortune.
From today on,
Jiang Lai is dead.
I'll take on a new identity
and a new face.
I'll arrange the surgery immediately.
(Day 1)
(From now on,)
(my name is Zhao Ke.)
(My new identity)
(and new face)
(were made specifically for you,
Zhang Haotian.)
(My dream of dancing,)
(my life,)
(my kidney...)
(I'll make you pay back every bit,
with interest.)
(Day 73)
(Two Months Later)
(Zhao Ke, Level One / Senior
Beauty Technician)
(My scars became my soil,)
(my struggles forged my strength,)
(and from the depths of despair,
I bloomed stronger than ever.)
(Lin Family Villa)
How did it go?
Don't worry.
I saw Jiang Lai being cremated
at the funeral home.
It's better she's dead.
Then it's all over.
But my mother-in-law still
doesn't trust me.
I signed a prenuptial
property agreement.
I'm nothing but an outsider now.
I can't touch a single cent
of the Lin family's fortune.
Then what do we do?
We can't let all our work go to waste.
If Madam Lin were gone,
everything in the Lin family
would belong to me.
Alright. I'll figure something out.
(Luna.S Beauty Salon)
Word has it that a top beauty technician
has returned from overseas.
And her services are priceless.
(Lin Lulu.)
(It's you.)
(You live comfortably,)
(enjoying everything my kidney
bought you.)
(While I was fighting for my life
in the hospital,)
(you were out there living it up.)
(But you're just another
one of his victims.)
(And you're the first step
in my revenge.)
I'm not as impressive as people say.
Hello, Miss Lin.
I wear gloves to keep my hands
at the right temperature.
I've also prepared a hot water bottle
and an ice bucket for you,
so you can adjust the temperature
whenever you need.
You really thought of everything.
You're blocking my view.
You want to serve me, yet you dare
give me that look?
(There's one more thing
I need to remind you.)
(In Lin Lulu's eyes,)
(people are divided
into different classes.)
(So you'd better be prepared.)
I'm sorry, Miss Lin.
It was my mistake.
I'll make sure to take good care of you.
You do have a rather cold
and aloof look.
I thought you were above
all worldly desires.
But I never expected
you'd be even more skilled
than my usual beauty technicians.
(Once I tear off Zhang Haotian's mask,)
(your arrogance will be worth nothing.)
(Rebirth)
♪Listen, the wind chimes softly whisper♪
♪I should forget you♪
♪But I have the will,
yet not the strength♪
♪To carry on♪
♪The scenery you once longed to see♪
♪You no longer have the strength♪
♪You want me to go there for you♪
♪I look up and see a hollow sky♪
♪Your freedom♪
♪Has become my cage♪
♪My hand brushes over your smile
in the photograph♪
♪This glass of wine is filled
with sorrow♪
♪I look up at the beautiful night sky♪
♪You told me♪
♪I would shine like a star♪
♪But you forgot to teach me♪
♪How to live without you♪
♪I look up♪
♪The starry sky♪
♪So hazy and blurred♪